let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
        option: [
            "Object-Oriented",
            "Object-Based",
            "Assembly-language",
            "high level",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: " Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
        option: [
            "Alternative to if-else",
            "Switch statement",
            "If-then-else statement",
            "immediate if",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
        option: [
            "Conditional block",
            "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
            "both conditional block and a single statement",
            "block that contains a single statement",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
        option: [
            "Shows a warning",
            "Prompts to complete the statement",
            "Throws an error",
            "Ignores the statements",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question:
            "The function and  var are known as:",
        option: [
            "Keywords",
            " Data types",
            " Declaration statements",
            "Prototypes",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: " Which of the following function of the String object returns the character in the string starting at the specified position via the specified number of characters?",
        option: ["slice() ", "split()", " substr()", "search()"],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: " In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
        option: [
            "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
            "Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
            "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
            "Both are not same at all.",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "If a function which does not return a value is known as _____",
        option: ["Static function", "Procedures", "Method", "Dynamic function"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "In a case, where the value of the operator is NULL , the typeof returned by the unary operator is___.",
        option: ["undefine", "string", "boolean", "object"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: " Which one of the following symbol is used for creating comments in the javascript:",
        option: ["//", "\\", "/**/", "\* */"],
        answer: 2,
    },
];
